Viewers all over the world, ask God for mercy and favour upon your life, upon your family.
Yes, the Lord says, rest - every area of your life!
Every area of your life you have challenges - I decree rest, in the name of Jesus!
In your health - receive rest, in the name of Jesus!
In your family and marriage - receive rest, in the name of Jesus!
With God, all things are possible!
It is possible! I say it is possible!
Receive rest, in the name of Jesus!
Yes, those challenges that are giving you sleepless nights -
it is time for rest, in the name of Jesus!
I say freedom! Freedom! Freedom! Freedom! Freedom! Freedom!
God knows you better.
Whatever area of your life that is giving you sleepless nights, giving you nightmares,
be released, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
I can feel it, I know you are released, in the name of Jesus!
I say, your are released, in the name of Jesus!
You are released in the name of Jesus!
Someone is somewhere releasing you right now -
in the person of the Holy Spirit!
Someone is busy releasing you!
Yes - continue to be released! Give thanks to God.
Give thanks to God!
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit and pray to meet you there again.
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God, as you send your testimony.
Engage with God.